[{"answer": " So, hows the first term of college life going", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 13, "question": "", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " So far so good.  I think Ive got the freshman fifteen, but other than that the onl", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 14, "question": " So, hows the first term of college life going", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " The commute?  What are you talking about?  Dont you live in the dorms", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 18, "question": " So far so good.  I think Ive got the freshman fifteen, but other than that the onl", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " No, I chose not to live in the dorms.  I got a cheap apartment, which is about 2", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 19, "question": " The commute?  What are you talking about?  Dont you live in the dorms", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Wow!  Thats pretty far.  Whyd you do that", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 23, "question": " No, I chose not to live in the dorms.  I got a cheap apartment, which is about 2", "qSentId": 22},{"answer": " Well, my brother works out there, and his roommate left, so I took the empt", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 24, "question": " Wow!  Thats pretty far.  Whyd you do that", "qSentId": 23},{"answer": " Oh, I see.  That makes sense.  So, how do you get to campus?  Bus", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 27, "question": " Well, my brother works out there, and his roommate left, so I took the empt", "qSentId": 26},{"answer": " No, I wish.  I looked into taking the bus, but there is no stop near our apartment", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 28, "question": " Oh, I see.  That makes sense.  So, how do you get to campus?  Bus", "qSentId": 27},{"answer": " How do you get to campus then", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 35, "question": " No, I wish.  I looked into taking the bus, but there is no stop near our apartment", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " I drive", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 36, "question": " How do you get to campus then", "qSentId": 35},{"answer": " Its not so bad, is it?  You said its only 25 miles", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 37, "question": " I drive", "qSentId": 36},{"answer": " Its not the distance thats a problem.  Its the traffic and the parking.  In th", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 38, "question": " Its not so bad, is it?  You said its only 25 miles", "qSentId": 37},{"answer": " Cant you reserve one", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 43, "question": " Its not the distance thats a problem.  Its the traffic and the parking.  In th", "qSentId": 42},{"answer": " No.  I pay $65 a month to park on campus, but we dont get assigned spaces.  So", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 44, "question": " Cant you reserve one", "qSentId": 43},{"answer": " Thats expensive, too", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 48, "question": " No.  I pay $65 a month to park on campus, but we dont get assigned spaces.  So", "qSentId": 47},{"answer": " I know.  I just cant figure out an alternative to driving", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 49, "question": " Thats expensive, too", "qSentId": 48},{"answer": " Theres no train around here, but I guess you could ride a bike", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 50, "question": " I know.  I just cant figure out an alternative to driving", "qSentId": 49},{"answer": " I dont know.  It seems kind of far to ride a bike.  Im so out of shape  I don", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 51, "question": " Theres no train around here, but I guess you could ride a bike", "qSentId": 50},{"answer": " I guess it is pretty far.  With all the rain and snow weve been having here latel", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 55, "question": " I dont know.  It seems kind of far to ride a bike.  Im so out of shape  I don", "qSentId": 54},{"answer": " Youre right.  It would be too difficult", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 59, "question": " I guess it is pretty far.  With all the rain and snow weve been having here latel", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " There is one other idea that might help with your commute", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 60, "question": " Youre right.  It would be too difficult", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Whats that", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 61, "question": " There is one other idea that might help with your commute", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": "Carpooling", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 62, "question": " Whats that", "qSentId": 61},{"answer": " You know, I hadnt even thought of that", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 63, "question": "Carpooling", "qSentId": 62},{"answer": " You could find someone to ride with and then you could split the cost of parking", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 64, "question": " You know, I hadnt even thought of that", "qSentId": 63},{"answer": " Thats a good idea.  I wonder if I could find someone", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 68, "question": " You could find someone to ride with and then you could split the cost of parking", "qSentId": 67},{"answer": " There are lots of message boards on campus.  You could post an ad there", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Thats a good idea.  I wonder if I could find someone", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " OK", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 70, "question": " There are lots of message boards on campus.  You could post an ad there", "qSentId": 69},{"answer": " Or, you could send out an email to the campus listserv.  I bet someone woul", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 74, "question": " OK", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " Youre right.  I think Im going to try that.  It definitely sounds like it might make m", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 78, "question": " Or, you could send out an email to the campus listserv.  I bet someone woul", "qSentId": 77},{"answer": " There you go.  Arent you glad you had lunch with me now", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 82, "question": " Youre right.  I think Im going to try that.  It definitely sounds like it might make m", "qSentId": 81},{"answer": " I am!  Thanks Mark", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 83, "question": " There you go.  Arent you glad you had lunch with me now", "qSentId": 82},{"answer": " No problem.  Listen, Ive got to go to class now, but let me know how you", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 84, "question": " I am!  Thanks Mark", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " I will.  Have fun in class", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 88, "question": " No problem.  Listen, Ive got to go to class now, but let me know how you", "qSentId": 87},{"answer": " See ya", "docId": "05-05", "aSentId": 89, "question": " I will.  Have fun in class", "qSentId": 88}]
